<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Hexo</title>
  
  
  <link href="http://example.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://example.com/"/>
  <updated>2024-09-23T06:33:16.387Z</updated>
  <id>http://example.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>John Doe</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Binance News</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2024/09/23/binance-news/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2024/09/23/binance-news/</id>
    <published>2024-09-23T03:31:33.689Z</published>
    <updated>2024-09-23T06:33:16.387Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="Looking-to-Increase-Your-Commission-Earnings-Integrate-the-News-Bot-into-Your-Telegram-Groups-Channels"><a href="#Looking-to-Increase-Your-Commission-Earnings-Integrate-the-News-Bot-into-Your-Telegram-Groups-Channels" class="headerlink" title="Looking to Increase Your Commission Earnings? Integrate the News Bot into Your Telegram Groups&#x2F;Channels"></a>Looking to Increase Your Commission Earnings? Integrate the News Bot into Your Telegram Groups&#x2F;Channels</h1><p>Contact Binance News: <a href="mailto:&#98;&#x69;&#110;&#97;&#110;&#99;&#x65;&#x6e;&#101;&#119;&#x73;&#64;&#98;&#105;&#x6e;&#97;&#110;&#x63;&#101;&#46;&#99;&#111;&#x6d;">&#98;&#x69;&#110;&#97;&#110;&#99;&#x65;&#x6e;&#101;&#119;&#x73;&#64;&#98;&#105;&#x6e;&#97;&#110;&#x63;&#101;&#46;&#99;&#111;&#x6d;</a></p><p>How to Earn Commissions with Binance News?<br>Want to not only stimulate lively discussions within your community but also earn commissions? Binance News introduces a Telegram bot that shares carefully curated news articles selected by our expert editorial team. We extend a warm invitation for you to seamlessly integrate this bot into your Telegram communities, providing your users with up-to-the-minute news and market insights.</p><p>When sharing news pieces with your followers, the bot will integrate your referral ID into links. For every new user successfully referred to Binance via the links, the referrer will receive a commission on fees anytime the new referred user trades on any of Binance’s Spot or Margin markets. For more details, please refer to the <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/faq/frequently-asked-questions-on-binance-referral-pro-mode-6233094e540b4ea4ac50387d1518911b">FAQ</a>.</p><p>How Can You Get Started?</p><ol><li>Add the bot (@OfficialBinanceFeedBot) to your Telegram groups or channels and grant it permission to send messages.</li><li>Find your Referral ID for Referral Pro on <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/activity/referral?stopRedirectToActivity=true">this page</a>, and decide if you need to create a specific Referral ID for the bot.</li><li>After completing the two steps mentioned above, simply share your group or channel links along with your Referral ID with the Binance News team, and we’ll take care of the rest with our tech team.</li></ol><p>Note: Please contact us, and our technical team will assist you with the necessary configuration. Simply adding the bot as a group member will not successfully share news articles in the group. The bot is currently available in English, Simplified Chinese, and Traditional Chinese, with more languages coming soon.</p><p>Why Partner with Binance News?<br>Top-quality content for FREE<br>Traditionally, procuring content licenses from leading crypto media outlets could cost over USD 5000 monthly. Binance is revolutionizing this landscape by offering premium content to our valued partners at no cost.</p><p>Boost Your Credibility Through Partnership with Binance News<br>As the official news channel of the world’s largest crypto exchange, Binance News boasts the highest number of followers on Binance Square. This underscores the trust and reliance placed on Binance News. By seamlessly integrating Binance News content into your platform, you not only provide invaluable insights to your users but also enhance the credibility of your brand.</p><p>About Binance News<br><a href="https://www.binance.com/en/feed/news/all">Binance News</a> stands as the foremost news source within Binance Square, one of the world’s largest crypto communities. Committed to delivering real-time market data and the latest trends, Binance News ensures your audience remains consistently ahead in the dynamic realm of cryptocurrency.</p><p>Read More‣ <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/4629204968289?utm_source=BinanceNewsRSS">How Can Binance News RSS Feed Integration Elevate Your Website? Discover the Benefits!</a></p><h1 id="Michael-Saylor-Discusses-Urgency-Of-Acquiring-Bitcoin"><a href="#Michael-Saylor-Discusses-Urgency-Of-Acquiring-Bitcoin" class="headerlink" title="Michael Saylor Discusses Urgency Of Acquiring Bitcoin"></a>Michael Saylor Discusses Urgency Of Acquiring Bitcoin</h1><p>According to Odaily, MicroStrategy founder Michael Saylor recently shared his thoughts on Bitcoin acquisition during an interview. Saylor emphasized the urgency that often accompanies the decision to invest in Bitcoin. He stated, ‘Once you acquire Bitcoin and develop an interest in it, your immediate reaction is to buy as much Bitcoin as possible because others will take all of your Bitcoin.’</p><p>Read More‣ <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/13880953553985?utm_source=BinanceNewsRSS">Michael Saylor Discusses Urgency Of Acquiring Bitcoin</a></p><h1 id="Fed’s-Approach-to-Rate-Cuts-Criticized-By-EY-Economist"><a href="#Fed’s-Approach-to-Rate-Cuts-Criticized-By-EY-Economist" class="headerlink" title="Fed’s Approach to Rate Cuts Criticized By EY Economist"></a>Fed’s Approach to Rate Cuts Criticized By EY Economist</h1><p>According to BlockBeats, on September 22, EY Chief Economist Gregory Daco criticized the Federal Reserve for being reactive rather than proactive in its approach to rate cuts. Daco highlighted concerns that the Fed might be waiting too long to take action, especially after data released two days following the July meeting showed an increase in the unemployment rate to 4.3%. He emphasized the need for the Fed to adopt a robust forward-looking framework instead of relying on data-driven decisions, which he believes they have yet to achieve.</p><p>Daco also pointed out a discrepancy between Wall Street’s expectations and the Fed’s projections regarding future rate cuts. While Wall Street anticipates more rate cuts, Fed policymakers estimate two more 25 basis point cuts by the end of 2024 and four additional cuts in 2025. The Fed’s rate-setting committee is nearly evenly split on the expected number of additional rate cuts this year, with seven policymakers supporting a 25 basis point cut by year-end and nine members favoring an additional 50 basis point cut. Two policymakers do not foresee any further cuts. This division suggests that while some officials might support a 25 basis point cut this month, others might opt for a 50 basis point cut to prevent further deterioration in the job market.</p><p>Read More‣ <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/13880943707489?utm_source=BinanceNewsRSS">Fed’s Approach to Rate Cuts Criticized By EY Economist</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;Looking-to-Increase-Your-Commission-Earnings-Integrate-the-News-Bot-into-Your-Telegram-Groups-Channels&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Looking-to-Increas</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>My Journey as a Newbie in the Crypto World - First Steps on Binance</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2024/09/17/hello-crypto/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2024/09/17/hello-crypto/</id>
    <published>2024-09-17T07:14:24.666Z</published>
    <updated>2024-09-17T08:53:06.933Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>&ensp;&ensp;As a newcomer to the exciting world of cryptocurrencies, I am thrilled to share my experiences and learnings with all of you.  Just recently, I took the plunge and registered an account on Binance, one of the leading cryptocurrency exchanges.  With a mix of excitement and trepidation, I am now ready to embark on my first steps in the realm of real-world crypto trading.<br>&ensp;&ensp;I must admit, when I first heard about Bitcoin and other digital currencies, I was both intrigued and intimidated.  The concept of decentralized finance and the volatility of the crypto market seemed daunting.  However, the more I learned about the potential of blockchain technology and the transformative power of cryptocurrencies, the more I felt compelled to dive in and become an active participant.<br><img src="https://github.com/WuKuida/WuKuida.github.io/blob/main/css/images/btc.jpeg?raw=true" alt="Bitcoin Wallet"><br>&ensp;&ensp;Registering on Binance was my first major milestone.  As I navigated through the user-friendly platform, I was impressed by the wide range of features and the depth of information available.  From understanding the different trading pairs to familiarizing myself with the order types, I have been meticulously studying every aspect to ensure I make informed decisions.<br>&ensp;&ensp;One of my primary goals is to start engaging in live trading.  I know that this will be a steep learning curve, but I am determined to approach it with an open mind and a willingness to learn from my mistakes.  I am eager to explore the various trading strategies, analyze market trends, and develop a sound understanding of risk management.<br>&ensp;&ensp;To aid my journey, I have been actively seeking out educational resources, both within the Binance community and across the broader crypto ecosystem.  I have been reading articles, watching tutorials, and participating in online discussions to expand my knowledge and connect with like-minded individuals.<br>&ensp;&ensp;My hope is that through this process, I can not only grow as a trader but also contribute to the growth and development of the crypto community.  I believe that by sharing our experiences, insights, and best practices, we can collectively elevate the understanding and adoption of cryptocurrencies.<br>&ensp;&ensp;As I take my first steps in the crypto world, I am filled with a sense of excitement and anticipation.  I know that the road ahead may be challenging, but I am committed to learning, adapting, and ultimately, finding success in this dynamic and ever-evolving landscape.  I look forward to connecting with fellow crypto enthusiasts, exchanging ideas, and embarking on this thrilling journey together.</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;&amp;ensp;&amp;ensp;As a newcomer to the exciting world of cryptocurrencies, I am thrilled to share my experiences and learnings with all of you.</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
